{
	"ExternalData": [
		{
		"txtVar_1":{
				"text" :"Please choose the correct option.",
				"description" :""
			} ,
			"txtVar_2":{
				"text" :"Select all that apply.",
				"description" :""
			} ,	
			"txtVar_3":{
				"text" :"Please choose the correct option.",
				"description" :""
			} ,
			"submitTxt":{
				"text" :"Submit",
				"description" :""
			},
			"tryAgainText":{
				"text" :"Try again",
				"description" :""
			},
			"solutionText":{
				"text" :"Solution",
				"description" :""
			},
			"scoreText":{
				"text" :"Score",
				"description" :""
			},		
			"randomizationOption":{"type" :"question","questionsineachModule" :"0","questionsineachObjective" :"0","numberofQuestionstodisplayed" :"10","assessmentTime" :"00:05:00","randomzetypeselected" : "no"  },"Modules": [{"id":1,"name":"mod_name","objectives":[{"objid":2,"objName":"obj_name","questions":[{"qusid":"349","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"TRF","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"Rm9yIHdvcmRzIHRoYXQgZW5kIGluIC1vdXIgaW4gQnJpdGlzaCBFbmdsaXNoLCBvZnRlbiB0aGUgInUiIGlzIGRyb3BwZWQgaW4gQW1lcmljYW4gRW5nbGlzaC4=","options":["VHJ1ZQ==","RmFsc2U="],"correctAnswer":"1","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"359","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"TRF","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"SWRlbnRpZnkgd2hldGhlciB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHNlbnRlbmNlIGNvbnRhaW5zIEFtZXJpY2FuIG9yIEJyaXRpc2ggc3BlbGxpbmdzOiBUaGUgZXhwZXJpbWVudHMgbXVzdCBiZSBjb25kdWN0ZWQgd2l0aCBkdWUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyByaWdvci4=","options":["VHJ1ZQ==","RmFsc2U="],"correctAnswer":"1","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"368","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"MCQ","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"YXN4ZGN2","options":["dW5kZWZpbmVk","dW5kZWZpbmVk","dW5kZWZpbmVk","ZHhkZGQ="],"correctAnswer":"4","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"391","qusCategory":"image","qusType":"TRF","qusImage":"yes","optnImage":"no","question":"VFJGIEltYWdl","options":["VHJ1ZQ==","RmFsc2U="],"correctAnswer":"1","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"389","qusCategory":"image","qusType":"MCQ","qusImage":"yes","optnImage":"yes","question":"SW1hZ2Vz","options":["NWIxNGY2ZjU2OGU2NzE1MjgxMDA1OTc5IERhc2hib2FyZCAoMSkuanBn","NWIxNGY2ZjU2OThlNDE1MjgxMDA1OTc5IERhc2hib2FyZC5qcGc=","NWIxNGY2ZjU2YTMzOTE1MjgxMDA1OTcxOC5qcGc=","NWIxNGY2ZjU2YWYyYTE1MjgxMDA1OTc1OV9NYW5hZ2UgVXNlcnMuanBn"],"correctAnswer":"4","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"346","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"MMCQ","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"PGRpdj5fX19fX19fX19fX18gaXMgdGhlJm5ic3A7PHNwYW4gc3R5bGU9ImZvbnQtd2VpZ2h0OiBib2xkOyI+Zmxvdzwvc3Bhbj4mbmJzcDtvZiBlbGVjdHJpYyBjaGFyZ2UgZnJvbSBvbmUgcGxhY2UgdG8gYW5vdGhlci4gX19fX19fX19fX19fIGlzIHRoZSZuYnNwOzxzcGFuIHN0eWxlPSJmb250LXdlaWdodDogYm9sZDsiPmZsb3c8L3NwYW4+Jm5ic3A7b2YgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2hhcmdlIGZyb20gb25lIHBsYWNlIHRvIGFub3RoZXIuIF9fX19fX19fX19fXyBpcyB0aGUmbmJzcDs8c3BhbiBzdHlsZT0iZm9udC13ZWlnaHQ6IGJvbGQ7Ij5mbG93PC9zcGFuPiZuYnNwO29mIGVsZWN0cmljIGNoYXJnZSBmcm9tIG9uZSBwbGFjZSB0byBhbm90aGVyLjxicj48L2Rpdj4=","options":["SXQgaXMgYSBtYXR0ZXIgb2YgZ3JlYXQgaG9ub3VyIHRvIHN0dWR5IGF0IEhhcnZhcmQu","VGhpcyBraW5kIG9mIGJlaGF2aW9yIGlzIHRvdGFsbHkgdW5hY2NlcHRhYmxlLg==","RG8geW91IHJlbWVtYmVyIHRoZSBjb2xvciBvZiBoZXIgZXllcz8=","V2hvIGlzIHlvdXIgZmF2b3VyaXRlIGF1dGhvcj8="],"correctAnswer":"1,4","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"356","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"TRF","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"SWRlbnRpZnkgd2hldGhlciB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHNlbnRlbmNlIGNvbnRhaW5zIEJyaXRpc2ggb3IgQW1lcmljYW4gc3BlbGxpbmc6IFRoZSBzb2xkaWVyJ3MgdmFsb3IgZWFybmVkIGhpbSBhIG1lZGFsIG9mIGhvbm9yLg==","options":["VHJ1ZQ==","RmFsc2U="],"correctAnswer":"2","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"358","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"MMCQ","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"SWRlbnRpZnkgdGhlIHNlbnRlbmNlcyB3aXRoIEJyaXRpc2ggc3BlbGxpbmdzLg==","options":["VGhlIHNvdXAgaGFkIGEgbmljZSBhbmQgdGFuZ3kgZmxhdm9yLCBsaWtlIHNwaWNlZCBidXR0ZXIu","VGhlIGtpbmdkb20gaGFkIGEgd2VsbC1lcXVpcHBlZCBhcm1vdXJ5Lg==","SmFjaydzIGRpc3J1cHRpdmUgZGVtZWFub3IgZ290IGhpbSBraWNrZWQgb3V0IG9mIHNjaG9vbCBmb3IgYSB3ZWVrLg==","SGUgc2F2b3VyZWQgdGhlIG1lbW9yaWVzIG9mIGhpcyB2YWNhdGlvbi4="],"correctAnswer":"1,3","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"351","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"MMCQ","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"RnJvbSB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nLCBpZGVudGlmeSB0aGUgc2VudGVuY2VzIHdpdGggQW1lcmljYW4gc3BlbGxpbmdzLg==","options":["R3ltbmFzdGljcyB0cmFpbmluZyBjYWxscyBmb3IgYSBncmVhdCBkZWFsIG9mIHJpZ29yLg==","U2hlIHdhcyBibGluZGVkIGJ5IHRoZSBnbGFtb3VyIG9mIHRoZSBmYXNoaW9uIHdvcmxkLg==","TWVldCBTYW0sIG15IG5laWdoYm9yIGZyb20gRGFsbGFzLg==","V2F0ZXIgaGFzIG5vIG9kb3Iu"],"correctAnswer":"1,3,4","modid":"791"},{"qusid":"352","qusCategory":"text","qusType":"MMCQ","qusImage":"no","optnImage":"no","question":"SWRlbnRpZnkgdGhlIHNlbnRlbmNlcyB3aXRoIEJyaXRpc2ggc3BlbGxpbmdzIGZyb20gdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZy4=","options":["VGhlIFNhdmlvdXIgcHJlYWNoZWQgbG92ZSBmb3IgYWxsLg==","QnkgdGhlIHRpbWUgdGhleSByZWFjaGVkIHRoZSBob3NwaXRhbCwgc2hlIHdhcyBhbHJlYWR5IGluIGxhYm9yLg==","UnVtb3IgaGFzIGl0IHRoYXQgdGhpcyBjb21wYW55IGlzIHNpbmtpbmcu","SGUgc3RpbGwgaGFyYm91cnMgZGVlcCBmZWVsaW5ncyBvZiByZXNlbnRtZW50IHRvd2FyZCBoaXMgZm9ybWVyIGVtcGxveWVyLg=="],"correctAnswer":"1","modid":"791"}]}]}]
			

		}
	]
}	
		